STEN MAYUNGA

SUMMARY

I am a highly analytical and motivated individual, with experience in developing dynamic web applications and software. My main strengths are in my problem solving skills, communication and working on my own initiative as a self taught developer. I have completed numerous paid and unpaid real-world projects to showcase my competent use of front and back-end technologies, most of which can be found on my portfolio website: https://stentech.dev

CONTACT

Dartford, Kent

+447861638448

stentechdev@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/stentechdev

@StenTechDev

EDUCATION

London App Brewery Full Stack Bootcamp

University of Kent BSc (Hons)



Visit my portfolio website

https://stentech.dev

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Freelance: 2020-Present

I have been designing and creating website as a hobby and freelance web developer since 2020. I have used content management systems such as Wix, Shopify and Wordpress to create websites and have become familiar with Liquid and PHP as a result. My current programming language is JavaScript and want to continue to add more languages to my repertoire. I am constantly learning and willing to adapt my technologies to best suit the projects I work on. I currently use the MERN stack.

Full Stack Developer, London App Brewery: 2021-2022

During my time studying and working on project at the London App Brewery bootcamp, I learn an extensive list of technologies and tools which included: JS ES6, JQuery, Node.js, APIs, SQL, React.js just to name a few as well as Backend and Front-End Web Development. At the end of the bootcamp, I developed over 25 websites, some of which can be found on my portfolio website.

Technical Support Specialist, Bose Corporation: 2020-2021

Helping customers from all over the world get the best from their Bose products by troubleshooting their problems and guiding them through how to solve them. A typical day entailed engaging with the customers, using a variety of tools and techniques to troubleshoot problems and resolving them in a timely manner. I used in depth technical knowledge and excellent customer service to achieve my daily goals as I worked with strict deadlines.

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap 4

JS ES6

DOM Manipulation

JQuery

Bash Command Line •

Git

GitHub

Version Control •

Node.js

NPM, Express.js

EJS, REST

APIs

SQL

Databases

React.is React Hooks

Firebase

MongoDB

Mongoose

Authentication

Deployment

Heroic & MongoDB Atlas